<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Homepage on DevDocs Navigation Menu Test</title>
    <link>https://danielmaharry-okta.github.io:1313/iaproto/index.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in Homepage on DevDocs Navigation Menu Test</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://danielmaharry-okta.github.io:1313/iaproto/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Learn</title>
      <link>https://danielmaharry-okta.github.io:1313/iaproto/learn/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://danielmaharry-okta.github.io:1313/iaproto/learn/index.html</guid>
      <description>Learn about Okta and Identity Access Management Click here to give feedback about this page
Group Notes Group description: - The &amp;ldquo;Learn&amp;rdquo; section guides developers new to IAM and/or Okta through the basics of OAuth, IAM, and Okta&amp;rsquo;s products.
The goal of this section is to empower these developers to be successful in developing applications using Okta&amp;rsquo;s products. It serves as a one-stop resource for understanding Okta&amp;rsquo;s products&amp;rsquo; features, the necessary tools for development, and industry best practices, ensuring developers have a solid foundation to start building secure and efficient applications.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plan</title>
      <link>https://danielmaharry-okta.github.io:1313/iaproto/plan/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://danielmaharry-okta.github.io:1313/iaproto/plan/index.html</guid>
      <description>Plan Click here to give feedback about this page
Group Notes Group description: The plan group&amp;rsquo;s scope includes:
Content focused on readers wanting to understand how to plan out their IAM solutions strategically and holistically. The content includes: Available access control strategies Available authentication methods (MFA, biometrics, etc) Policies Deployment considerations including topics such as: Availability Reliability Performance etc Best practices content Content Notes Target personas: WIC App Developer,Experienced IAM developer</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Build</title>
      <link>https://danielmaharry-okta.github.io:1313/iaproto/build/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://danielmaharry-okta.github.io:1313/iaproto/build/index.html</guid>
      <description>Build Click here to give feedback about this page
Group Notes Group description: This group is oriented toward developers looking for ways to integrate Okta with their applications. The types of docs focus specifically on:
Specific use cases Best practices The largest topics are:
LCM OIG Authenntication Automation Content Notes Target personas: WIC App Developer,Experienced IAM developer
Description: Sets up journeys and provides links to content under this node. See Guide Hub description for more details on the contents of this doc type.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Publish</title>
      <link>https://danielmaharry-okta.github.io:1313/iaproto/publish/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://danielmaharry-okta.github.io:1313/iaproto/publish/index.html</guid>
      <description>Publish Click here to give feedback about this page
Group Notes Group description: - Reasons for the name publish: - Aligned with the action/task based focus of the site - The ultimate goal of this section is to &amp;ldquo;Publish&amp;rdquo; on the OIN - Some user research evidence
Existing doc needs to be updated to reflect new changes to sub groups Content Notes Target personas: WIC App Developer,Experienced IAM developer
Changes to be made: - There was a discussion last year to update this doc since: - There was dissatisfaction from team members over the HTML format, and it&amp;rsquo;s overall content</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reference</title>
      <link>https://danielmaharry-okta.github.io:1313/iaproto/reference/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://danielmaharry-okta.github.io:1313/iaproto/reference/index.html</guid>
      <description>Reference Click here to give feedback about this page
Content Notes Target personas: WIC App Developer,Experienced IAM developer
Structure type: Navigation
Content type: Guide Hub
A guide hub is the main navigation page for a section, such as learn, plan, or build. It begins with &amp;ldquo;Who this section is for?&amp;rdquo; and how the user may have gotten to this page, i.e., where they are in their user journey at this point.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Other Links</title>
      <link>https://danielmaharry-okta.github.io:1313/iaproto/other-links/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://danielmaharry-okta.github.io:1313/iaproto/other-links/index.html</guid>
      <description>Other Links Click here to give feedback about this page
Content Notes Description: This area contains secondary content typically not found in the main navigation of the DevDocs site.
Structure type: Unknown
Content type: Not applicable
Not applicable</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>