<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Homepage :: DevDocs Navigation Menu Test</title>
    <link>https://danielmaharry-okta.github.io:1313/iaproto/</link>
    <description>developer.okta.com Navigation prototype v3.0b1 Click here to give feedback about this page&#xA;Please give us your feedback on the redesigned navigation system for the developer documentation website.&#xA;The goal is a task-based navigation that makes it easier for developers to find the content they’re looking for… the answer to their question. We’ve biased the design to developers inexperienced with Identity and Access Management.&#xA;Please do NOT give us your feedback on the design and visuals of this prototype or its lack of actual documentation.</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://danielmaharry-okta.github.io:1313/iaproto/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Find your path</title>
      <link>https://danielmaharry-okta.github.io:1313/iaproto/find-your-path/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://danielmaharry-okta.github.io:1313/iaproto/find-your-path/</guid>
      <description>Find your path at Okta Click here to give feedback about this page&#xA;About This Page Page ID: 867&#xA;Is this a new page?: Completely new doc with new content&#xA;Target personas: Internal app builders, Saas Builder&#xA;Page type: Navigation&#xA;Content type: Guide Hub&#xA;A guide hub is the main navigation page for a section, such as learn, plan, or build. It begins with “Who this section is for?” and how the user may have gotten to this page, i.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn</title>
      <link>https://danielmaharry-okta.github.io:1313/iaproto/learn/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://danielmaharry-okta.github.io:1313/iaproto/learn/</guid>
      <description>Learn about Okta and Identity Access Management Click here to give feedback about this page&#xA;Section Notes The Learn section targets all developers new to Identity Access Management and/or Okta. It covers&#xA;An overview of the Workforce Identity Cloud (WIC) Basic IAM concepts and how Okta implements them Basic Okta-specific knowledge that all developers should know. An overview of Lifecycle Management The Okta Integration Network Tools for automating processes with Okta The goal of this section is to empower these developers to be successful in developing applications and OIN integrations using Okta’s products.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plan</title>
      <link>https://danielmaharry-okta.github.io:1313/iaproto/plan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://danielmaharry-okta.github.io:1313/iaproto/plan/</guid>
      <description>Plan and design your IAM solutions Click here to give feedback about this page&#xA;Section Notes The Plan section targets developers wanting to understand how to plan out their enterprise solutions and their app integration builds strategically and holistically. It covers:&#xA;Available access control strategies Available authentication methods (MFA, biometrics, etc) Policies Deployment considerations including topics such as: Availability Reliability Performance etc About This Page Page ID: 480&#xA;Is this a new page?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Build</title>
      <link>https://danielmaharry-okta.github.io:1313/iaproto/build/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://danielmaharry-okta.github.io:1313/iaproto/build/</guid>
      <description>Build Click here to give feedback about this page&#xA;Section Notes The Build section targets developers looking for ways to integrate Okta with their applications. Each doc focuses on a specific use case or set of best practices.&#xA;This section’s content is in usage order. That is, the first guides listed in the navigation are those developers are most likely to use first (Adding an authentication solution to an app) when building an application to those needed last (Reporting and Monitoring).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Publish</title>
      <link>https://danielmaharry-okta.github.io:1313/iaproto/publish/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://danielmaharry-okta.github.io:1313/iaproto/publish/</guid>
      <description>Publish an integration to the OIN Click here to give feedback about this page&#xA;Section Notes The Publish section contains all the information needed to submit, test and publish an integration to the Okta Integration Network.&#xA;About This Page Page ID: 354&#xA;Is this a new page?: Existing doc: changes are needed to update the doc and to fit the new IA&#xA;Target personas: Saas Builder&#xA;Description: Publish landing page draft: https://www.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reference</title>
      <link>https://danielmaharry-okta.github.io:1313/iaproto/reference/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://danielmaharry-okta.github.io:1313/iaproto/reference/</guid>
      <description>Reference Click here to give feedback about this page&#xA;About This Page Page ID: 172&#xA;Is this a new page?: Completely new doc with new content&#xA;Target personas: Internal app builders, Saas Builder&#xA;Page type: Navigation&#xA;Content type: Guide Hub&#xA;A guide hub is the main navigation page for a section, such as learn, plan, or build. It begins with “Who this section is for?” and how the user may have gotten to this page, i.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>