<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Automation Tools :: DevDocs Navigation Menu Test</title>
    <link>https://danielmaharry-okta.github.io:1313/iaproto/learn/automation-tools/</link>
    <description>Okta Automation Tools Click here to give feedback about this page&#xA;About This Page Is this a new page?: Completely new doc with new content&#xA;Target personas: Internal application builders&#xA;Page type: Navigation&#xA;Content type: Autogenerated Index&#xA;An autogenerated index is an automatically generated list of links to topics immediately beneath it based purely on the site’s structure, or with some level of filtering. A blind list of summaries and links to child docs.</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://danielmaharry-okta.github.io:1313/iaproto/learn/automation-tools/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Okta Workflows</title>
      <link>https://danielmaharry-okta.github.io:1313/iaproto/learn/automation-tools/okta-workflows/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://danielmaharry-okta.github.io:1313/iaproto/learn/automation-tools/okta-workflows/</guid>
      <description>Okta Workflows Click here to give feedback about this page&#xA;About This Page Is this a new page?: Completely new doc with new content&#xA;Target personas: Internal application builders&#xA;Description: A developer’s introduction to Okta Workflows, what it is for, what problems it solves, and how developers write code against it (if at all). Are there any connections with SCIM and LCM applications and therefore the OIN for example? Also, make sure to compare and contrast with Connector Builder and Hooks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Workflow Connector Builder</title>
      <link>https://danielmaharry-okta.github.io:1313/iaproto/learn/automation-tools/workflow-connector-builder/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://danielmaharry-okta.github.io:1313/iaproto/learn/automation-tools/workflow-connector-builder/</guid>
      <description>Workflow Connector Builder Click here to give feedback about this page&#xA;About This Page Is this a new page?: Completely new doc with new content&#xA;Target personas: Internal application builders&#xA;Description: A brief introduction to Workflows Connector Builder that distinguishes it from Okta Workflows the Platform and what hooks are for. Note that WCB can create flows that can also be submitted to OIN. Then redirect to the help doc area.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hooks</title>
      <link>https://danielmaharry-okta.github.io:1313/iaproto/learn/automation-tools/hooks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://danielmaharry-okta.github.io:1313/iaproto/learn/automation-tools/hooks/</guid>
      <description>Inline and Event Hooks Click here to give feedback about this page&#xA;About This Page Is this a new page?: Existing doc: changes are needed to update the doc and to fit the new IA&#xA;Target personas: Internal application builders&#xA;Description: An overview of event and inline hooks, what they are, and some basic use cases. Establish the difference between hooks and the Workflows platform, and then provide a link to the more detailed “How to Implement a hook section” (ID: 660)</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>