<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Publish on Hugo Techdoc Theme</title>
    <link>https://danielmaharry-okta.github.io:1313/iaproto/ia-navigation/publish/index.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in Publish on Hugo Techdoc Theme</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://danielmaharry-okta.github.io:1313/iaproto/ia-navigation/publish/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Learn about the Okta Integration Network</title>
      <link>https://danielmaharry-okta.github.io:1313/iaproto/ia-navigation/publish/learn-about-the-okta-integration-network/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://danielmaharry-okta.github.io:1313/iaproto/ia-navigation/publish/learn-about-the-okta-integration-network/index.html</guid>
      <description>Learn Click here to give feedback about this page
Content Notes Target personas: WIC App Developer,Experienced IAM developer
Why is this here?: Reasons for a &amp;ldquo;Learn&amp;rdquo; section include:
Internal OIN Workshop results: When asked &amp;ldquo;What do devs need to know about the OIN&amp;rdquo; employees answered: Why OIN What&amp;rsquo;s the value prop What is OIN? What does &amp;ldquo;Integration&amp;rdquo; mean? Whats the path to OIN success. All these points are described in this section When asked customers what&amp;rsquo;s missing in the OIN docs they answered: - Best practices, - Many comments on the need for use cases This section will cover the above customer feedback Content type: Guide Hub</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plan your app integration</title>
      <link>https://danielmaharry-okta.github.io:1313/iaproto/ia-navigation/publish/plan-your-app-integration/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://danielmaharry-okta.github.io:1313/iaproto/ia-navigation/publish/plan-your-app-integration/index.html</guid>
      <description>Plan your app integration Click here to give feedback about this page
Content Notes Target personas: WIC App Developer,Experienced IAM developer
Description: Discuss factors developers need to think about before being successful on the OIN
Why is this here?: - Internal Workshop: When asked, &amp;ldquo;What prevents developers from being successful on the OIN? devs answered: - &amp;ldquo;Docs focus on submission and not factors to think about before&amp;rdquo;
Content type: Explanation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Test with a sample app</title>
      <link>https://danielmaharry-okta.github.io:1313/iaproto/ia-navigation/publish/test-with-a-sample-app/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://danielmaharry-okta.github.io:1313/iaproto/ia-navigation/publish/test-with-a-sample-app/index.html</guid>
      <description>Test with a sample app Click here to give feedback about this page
Group Notes Group description: - Contains sample apps that customers can use to understand the configurations of an OIN app and ways to submit such an app.
The sample app can be the basis for the customer&amp;rsquo;s OIN app if they choose to use it. Content Notes Target personas: WIC App Developer,Experienced IAM developer
Content type: Guide Hub</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Build your app</title>
      <link>https://danielmaharry-okta.github.io:1313/iaproto/ia-navigation/publish/build-your-app/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://danielmaharry-okta.github.io:1313/iaproto/ia-navigation/publish/build-your-app/index.html</guid>
      <description>Build your app Click here to give feedback about this page
Content Notes Target personas: WIC App Developer,Experienced IAM developer
Description: This doc provides summaries and links to how to build an SSO app, LCM (SCIM) app, and API Service. No content to actually building these apps are located here
Links to original docs: &amp;lsquo;- SSO - Only include content and links to other docs that show how to build an SSO app.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prepare for submission</title>
      <link>https://danielmaharry-okta.github.io:1313/iaproto/ia-navigation/publish/prepare-for-submission/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://danielmaharry-okta.github.io:1313/iaproto/ia-navigation/publish/prepare-for-submission/index.html</guid>
      <description>Prepare for submission Click here to give feedback about this page
Content Notes Target personas: WIC App Developer,Experienced IAM developer
Content type: Guide Hub
This type of document serves as a central navigational starting point within a larger documentation system. It&amp;rsquo;s structured to outline various user journeys, guiding users to specific documents through organized links, often presented in a tree view or a similar hierarchical structure. Some key characteristics of a Guide Hub or Documentation Hub:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Submit</title>
      <link>https://danielmaharry-okta.github.io:1313/iaproto/ia-navigation/publish/submit/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://danielmaharry-okta.github.io:1313/iaproto/ia-navigation/publish/submit/index.html</guid>
      <description>Submit Click here to give feedback about this page
Content Notes Target personas: WIC App Developer,Experienced IAM developer
Changes to be made: This doc is large and covers different types of content such as guide up, submission process, etc. For now, it&amp;rsquo;s one doc, but we may need to split this up.
Links to original docs: - Publish an OIN integration: https://developer.okta.com/docs/guides/submit-app-overview/
Content type: Guide Hub
This type of document serves as a central navigational starting point within a larger documentation system.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Update your app</title>
      <link>https://danielmaharry-okta.github.io:1313/iaproto/ia-navigation/publish/update-your-app/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://danielmaharry-okta.github.io:1313/iaproto/ia-navigation/publish/update-your-app/index.html</guid>
      <description>Releasing new versions of your app Click here to give feedback about this page
Group Notes Group description: Based on the User research we need to determine what the content should be for this section.
Content Notes Target personas: WIC App Developer,Experienced IAM developer
Why is this here?: At Oktane, the OIN Survey showed several customers citing the following as &amp;ldquo;Missing info with the OIN Docs&amp;rdquo;:
Missing information from the app providers on their new versions SP Software version info Content type: Guide Hub</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Connect for help</title>
      <link>https://danielmaharry-okta.github.io:1313/iaproto/ia-navigation/publish/connect-for-help/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://danielmaharry-okta.github.io:1313/iaproto/ia-navigation/publish/connect-for-help/index.html</guid>
      <description>Connect Click here to give feedback about this page
Content Notes Target personas: WIC App Developer,Experienced IAM developer
Why is this here?: - Internal workshop: When asked &amp;ldquo;What prevents developers from being successful on the OIN&amp;rdquo;, respondents answered: - How to ask for and receive help from OKta - Links to Okta Education classes
Content type: Explanation
This content type is focused on more detailed, topic-specific discussions that clarify how certain features, functionalities, or aspects of the product or service operate.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>