<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Learn :: DevDocs Navigation Menu Test</title>
    <link>https://danielmaharry-okta.github.io:1313/iaproto/learn/</link>
    <description>Learn about Okta and Identity Access Management Click here to give feedback about this page&#xA;Section Notes The Learn section targets all developers new to Identity Access Management and/or Okta. It covers&#xA;An overview of the Workforce Identity Cloud (WIC) Basic IAM concepts and how Okta implements them Basic Okta-specific knowledge that all developers should know. An overview of Lifecycle Management The Okta Integration Network Tools for automating processes with Okta The goal of this section is to empower these developers to be successful in developing applications and OIN integrations using Okta’s products.</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://danielmaharry-okta.github.io:1313/iaproto/learn/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Identity and Access Management (IAM) cheat sheet</title>
      <link>https://danielmaharry-okta.github.io:1313/iaproto/learn/identity-and-access-management-iam-cheat-sheet/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://danielmaharry-okta.github.io:1313/iaproto/learn/identity-and-access-management-iam-cheat-sheet/</guid>
      <description>Identity and Access Management (IAM) cheat sheet Click here to give feedback about this page&#xA;About This Page Page ID: 807&#xA;Is this a new page?: Completely new doc with new content&#xA;Target personas: Internal app builders, Saas Builder&#xA;Description: Lists all the most relevant IAM and Okta’s acronyms. Outstanding questions that still need to be answered include:&#xA;Which acronyms should be listed? Is there a limit to how many acronyms?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Workforce Identity Cloud (WIC)</title>
      <link>https://danielmaharry-okta.github.io:1313/iaproto/learn/workforce-identity-cloud-wic/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://danielmaharry-okta.github.io:1313/iaproto/learn/workforce-identity-cloud-wic/</guid>
      <description>Workforce Identity Cloud (WIC) overview Click here to give feedback about this page&#xA;About This Page Page ID: 488&#xA;Is this a new page?: Completely new doc with new content&#xA;Target personas: Internal app builders, Saas Builder&#xA;Description: Explains WIC and compares it to the CIC domain. Describes the domain of what developer.okta.com covers. Draws the reader in with the problems they are trying to solve.&#xA;Why is this here?:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IAM fundamentals</title>
      <link>https://danielmaharry-okta.github.io:1313/iaproto/learn/iam-fundamentals/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://danielmaharry-okta.github.io:1313/iaproto/learn/iam-fundamentals/</guid>
      <description>IAM Overview Click here to give feedback about this page&#xA;About This Page Page ID: 846&#xA;Is this a new page?: Completely new doc with new content&#xA;Target personas: Internal app builders, Saas Builder&#xA;Description: Explains Identity Access Management at a high level. Include links to child docs in this group.&#xA;Links to original docs:&#xA;Identity and Access Management (IAM) overview: https://developer.okta.com/docs/concepts/iam-overview/&#xA;Why is this here?:&#xA;Respondents with IAM experience level lower that 5 say that they rarely come to the site.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Okta fundamentals</title>
      <link>https://danielmaharry-okta.github.io:1313/iaproto/learn/okta-fundamentals/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://danielmaharry-okta.github.io:1313/iaproto/learn/okta-fundamentals/</guid>
      <description>Okta fundamentals Click here to give feedback about this page&#xA;Section Notes The Okta Basics section gives new-to-IAM or new-to-Okta developers an introduction to Okta-specific basic concepts that they will need to build solutions that integrate with Okta.&#xA;About This Page Page ID: 144&#xA;Is this a new page?: Completely new doc with new content&#xA;Target personas: Internal app builders, Saas Builder&#xA;Why is this here?:&#xA;Respondents with an IAM experience level lower than 5 say that the developer docs “Needs improvement” Respondents with IAM experience level lower that 5 say that they rarely come to the site See Learn (ID: 1)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Okta Integration Network (OIN)</title>
      <link>https://danielmaharry-okta.github.io:1313/iaproto/learn/okta-integration-network-oin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://danielmaharry-okta.github.io:1313/iaproto/learn/okta-integration-network-oin/</guid>
      <description>Okta Integration Network (OIN) Click here to give feedback about this page&#xA;About This Page Page ID: 353&#xA;Is this a new page?: Completely new doc with new content&#xA;Target personas: Saas Builder&#xA;Description: An introduction to the OIN, what it is, what an integration is, different types of integration in the OIN, differences between OIN Manager and OIN Wizard, why publish to the OIN at all?&#xA;Lists reasons why people / ISVs should care about publishing on the OIN in the first place.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automation tools</title>
      <link>https://danielmaharry-okta.github.io:1313/iaproto/learn/automation-tools/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://danielmaharry-okta.github.io:1313/iaproto/learn/automation-tools/</guid>
      <description>Okta automation tools Click here to give feedback about this page&#xA;About This Page Page ID: 357&#xA;Is this a new page?: Completely new doc with new content&#xA;Target personas: Internal app builders&#xA;Page type: Navigation&#xA;Content type: Autogenerated Index&#xA;An autogenerated index is an automatically generated list of links to topics immediately beneath it based purely on the site’s structure, or with some level of filtering. A blind list of summaries and links to child docs.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>