<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Plan :: DevDocs Navigation Menu Test</title>
    <link>https://danielmaharry-okta.github.io:1313/iaproto/plan/</link>
    <description>Plan and design your IAM solutions Click here to give feedback about this page&#xA;Section Notes The Plan section targets developers wanting to understand how to plan out their enterprise solutions and their app integration builds strategically and holistically. It covers:&#xA;Available access control strategies Available authentication methods (MFA, biometrics, etc) Policies Deployment considerations including topics such as: Availability Reliability Performance etc About This Page Page ID: 480&#xA;Is this a new page?</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://danielmaharry-okta.github.io:1313/iaproto/plan/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Design your IAM enterprise architecture</title>
      <link>https://danielmaharry-okta.github.io:1313/iaproto/plan/design-your-iam-enterprise-architecture/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://danielmaharry-okta.github.io:1313/iaproto/plan/design-your-iam-enterprise-architecture/</guid>
      <description>Design an IAM Solution: From Authentication to Compliance Click here to give feedback about this page&#xA;About This Page Page ID: 484&#xA;Is this a new page?: Existing doc: changes are needed to update the doc and to fit the new IA&#xA;Target personas: Internal app builders, Saas Builder&#xA;Changes to be made:&#xA;Phase 1: CIAM content needs to be removed. Phase 2: Remove IAM overview content and place it in the IAM overview doc.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Decide which integrations to build</title>
      <link>https://danielmaharry-okta.github.io:1313/iaproto/plan/decide-which-integrations-to-build/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://danielmaharry-okta.github.io:1313/iaproto/plan/decide-which-integrations-to-build/</guid>
      <description>Decide which integrations to build to enter the market Click here to give feedback about this page&#xA;About This Page Page ID: 808&#xA;Is this a new page?: Completely new doc with new content&#xA;Target personas: Saas Builder&#xA;Description:&#xA;Demisitfy the term “integrations” here. The term is too overloaded. The doc’s contents need to be workshopped. Discuss with Jeff the specific content for this doc. Jeff’s original title for this doc was: “What integrations should I build to enter the market?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plan your app integration</title>
      <link>https://danielmaharry-okta.github.io:1313/iaproto/plan/plan-your-app-integration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://danielmaharry-okta.github.io:1313/iaproto/plan/plan-your-app-integration/</guid>
      <description>Plan your Okta app integration Click here to give feedback about this page&#xA;About This Page Page ID: 796&#xA;Is this a new page?: Completely new doc with new content&#xA;Target personas: Internal app builders, Saas Builder&#xA;Page type: Navigation&#xA;Content type: Autogenerated Index&#xA;An autogenerated index is an automatically generated list of links to topics immediately beneath it based purely on the site’s structure, or with some level of filtering.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Design for automation</title>
      <link>https://danielmaharry-okta.github.io:1313/iaproto/plan/design-for-automation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://danielmaharry-okta.github.io:1313/iaproto/plan/design-for-automation/</guid>
      <description>Automation Click here to give feedback about this page&#xA;About This Page Page ID: 819&#xA;Is this a new page?: Completely new doc with new content&#xA;Target personas: Internal app builders, Saas Builder&#xA;Page type: Navigation&#xA;Content type: Autogenerated Index&#xA;An autogenerated index is an automatically generated list of links to topics immediately beneath it based purely on the site’s structure, or with some level of filtering. A blind list of summaries and links to child docs.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>