<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Publish on DevDocs Navigation Menu Test</title>
    <link>https://danielmaharry-okta.github.io:1313/iaproto/publish/index.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in Publish on DevDocs Navigation Menu Test</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://danielmaharry-okta.github.io:1313/iaproto/publish/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Review the OIN restrictions</title>
      <link>https://danielmaharry-okta.github.io:1313/iaproto/publish/review-the-oin-restrictions/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://danielmaharry-okta.github.io:1313/iaproto/publish/review-the-oin-restrictions/index.html</guid>
      <description>Review the OIN restrictions Click here to give feedback about this page
Content Notes Target personas: WIC App Developer,Experienced IAM developer
Description: The &amp;ldquo;OIN Limitations&amp;rdquo; section from the pre-requisites page. This is being pulled out separately as it is linked to in many other pages compares to the pre-reqs in general and it needs to be easier to find in the navigation as a result.
Changes to be made: Update with any UL or SCIM Entitlements limitations if there are any</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Review the OIN submission requirements</title>
      <link>https://danielmaharry-okta.github.io:1313/iaproto/publish/review-the-oin-submission-requirements/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://danielmaharry-okta.github.io:1313/iaproto/publish/review-the-oin-submission-requirements/index.html</guid>
      <description>Review the OIN submission requirements Click here to give feedback about this page
Content Notes Target personas: WIC App Developer,Experienced IAM developer
Description: Basically the existing OIN pre-reqs page minue the OIN limitations page which is being split out into its own page - &amp;ldquo;OIN Restrictions&amp;rdquo;
Changes to be made: Update with any UL or SCIm Entitlements pre-reqs if there are any
Links to original docs: - OIN submission requirements: https://developer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Submit your integration to OIN</title>
      <link>https://danielmaharry-okta.github.io:1313/iaproto/publish/submit-your-integration-to-oin/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://danielmaharry-okta.github.io:1313/iaproto/publish/submit-your-integration-to-oin/index.html</guid>
      <description>Submitting a new app integration to the OIN Click here to give feedback about this page
Content Notes Target personas: WIC App Developer,Experienced IAM developer
Structure type: Navigation
Content type: Autogenerated Index
An autogenerated index is an automatically generated list of links to topics immediately beneath it based purely on the site&amp;rsquo;s structure, or with some level of filtering. A blind list of summaries and links to child docs. For example:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Update your integration</title>
      <link>https://danielmaharry-okta.github.io:1313/iaproto/publish/update-your-integration/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://danielmaharry-okta.github.io:1313/iaproto/publish/update-your-integration/index.html</guid>
      <description>Releasing new versions of your app Click here to give feedback about this page
Group Notes Group description: Based on the User research we need to determine what the content should be for this section.
Content Notes Target personas: WIC App Developer,Experienced IAM developer
Why is this here?: At Oktane, the OIN Survey showed several customers citing the following as &amp;ldquo;Missing info with the OIN Docs&amp;rdquo;:
Missing information from the app providers on their new versions SP Software version info Structure type: Navigation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Find help for OIN problems</title>
      <link>https://danielmaharry-okta.github.io:1313/iaproto/publish/find-help-for-oin-problems/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://danielmaharry-okta.github.io:1313/iaproto/publish/find-help-for-oin-problems/index.html</guid>
      <description>Find help for OIN problems Click here to give feedback about this page
Content Notes Target personas: WIC App Developer,Experienced IAM developer
Description: The goal of this page is to give links to OIN related education courses, OIN support communites, sites where they need to talk to sales, etc.
Why is this here?: - Internal workshop: When asked &amp;ldquo;What prevents developers from being successful on the OIN&amp;rdquo;, respondents answered: - How to ask for and receive help from OKta - Links to Okta Education classes</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>