<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Plan your build :: DevDocs Navigation Menu Test</title>
    <link>https://danielmaharry-okta.github.io:1313/iaproto/plan/plan-your-build/</link>
    <description>Plan your build Click here to give feedback about this page&#xA;Content Notes Target personas: New IAM Developers,Developers new to Okta&#xA;Structure type: Navigation&#xA;Content type: Autogenerated Index An autogenerated index is an automatically generated list of links to topics immediately beneath it based purely on the site’s structure, or with some level of filtering. A blind list of summaries and links to child docs.</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://danielmaharry-okta.github.io:1313/iaproto/plan/plan-your-build/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Plan your lifecycle manegement application build</title>
      <link>https://danielmaharry-okta.github.io:1313/iaproto/plan/plan-your-build/plan-your-lifecycle-manegement-application-build/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://danielmaharry-okta.github.io:1313/iaproto/plan/plan-your-build/plan-your-lifecycle-manegement-application-build/</guid>
      <description>Plan your lifecycle management application build Click here to give feedback about this page&#xA;Content Notes Target personas: New IAM Developers,Developers new to Okta&#xA;Changes to be made: For best effect, it makes sense to rework these articles to match “Plan your web application build” - i.e., to have a How-To \ Guide Hub style article that runs through the entire process of building a lifecycle-aware app. “Prepare your SCIM API service” Article has two distinct sections: “Preparation”, and “Test it works as a private App” “Connect Your SCIM API service to Okta” covers creating a SCIM app integration in the Admin Console “Test Your Okta SCIM integration” covers another set of tests for your app once it is set up as an Okta integration and links to another set of tests to run before submission process is complete Links to original docs: + https://developer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plan your service application build</title>
      <link>https://danielmaharry-okta.github.io:1313/iaproto/plan/plan-your-build/plan-your-service-application-build/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://danielmaharry-okta.github.io:1313/iaproto/plan/plan-your-build/plan-your-service-application-build/</guid>
      <description>Plan your service application build Click here to give feedback about this page&#xA;Content Notes Target personas: New IAM Developers,Developers new to Okta&#xA;Changes to be made: For best effect, it makes sense to rework these articles to match “Plan your web application build - i.e., to have a How-To \ Guide Hub style article that runs through the entire process of building a lifecycle-aware app.&#xA;Links to original docs: + https://developer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plan your web application build</title>
      <link>https://danielmaharry-okta.github.io:1313/iaproto/plan/plan-your-build/plan-your-web-application-build/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://danielmaharry-okta.github.io:1313/iaproto/plan/plan-your-build/plan-your-web-application-build/</guid>
      <description>Plan your web application build Click here to give feedback about this page&#xA;Content Notes Target personas: New IAM Developers,Developers new to Okta&#xA;Description: + This article presents a full overview of all the steps needed to build a web app and configure a web app integration It is interspersed with notes on what to include or not for OIN submission. It refers to SSO but never explains what specifically makes it support SSO.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>